《生活大爆炸》前情提要
Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
想去吃午饭吗
Want to grab some lunch?
你猜怎么着  不去
You know what? I don't think so.
我来猜猜看  你不吃饭
Oh, let me guess, you're not eating
是因为刻薄女们用笔把你胖的部位圈出来了
because the mean girls circled your chubby bits in marker?
不  是这个  你刚才说的这个
No. That, that right there.
这就是原因  你总是在取笑我
That's the reason. You're always making fun of me.
那些都是玩笑话而已
Those are just jokes.
我用这种方式来表达我们是朋友
It's my way of saying that we're friends,
再说你减个几斤又不会死
and it wouldn't hurt you to drop a few.
15年来你总是在奚落我
15 years of constant ridicule.
我觉得我们的关系已经变得有毒了
I-I think our relationship has become toxic.
你这是什么意思
What are you saying?
我觉得我们需要分开一段时间
I think you and I need to spend some time away from each other.
听着  我...
Look, I...
看得出你不开心  但是...
I can see you're upset, but...
我需要知道一些基本规则
I'm gonna need some ground rules.
分开期间  我能否约其他缠人的印度男
While we're apart, can I see other needy Indian men?
滚出去
Get out!
时至今日
斯图尔特  我有两个问题
Oh, Stuart, two questions:
你有最新的《水行侠》漫画吗
Do you have the new Aquaman,
还有你介不介意我在你后屋熏肉
and do you mind if I use your back room to smoke some meat?
鉴于问的人是你
Well, since it's you asking,
我猜熏肉应该没有别的隐晦含义
I'm gonna guess that's not a euphemism.
所以你为什么要熏肉啊
Why are you smoking meat?
还有你为什么开始看《水行侠》这种玩意了
And why are you reading Aquaman?
我想给艾米做一顿符合历史的
I am trying to make Amy a historically accurate
1932年出版的背景设在1870到80年间的美国大西部拓荒风格儿童小说
《草原小屋》风格生日晚餐  至于漫画...
Little House on the Prairie dinner for her birthday, and...
则是以防日后它火的时候好显摆自己早看过了
I want to be able to say I was reading it before it was cool.
还真是有心呢
Wow, well, that's actually really sweet.
水行侠曾是人气低又总被漫迷吐槽的弱鸡侠  直到新的电影中找了型男演出才翻身
我是说晚餐的事  《水行侠》的事太傻逼了
The dinner thing. The Aquaman thing's dumb.
对了  哈雷的生日跟艾米生日同天对吧
Isn't Halley's birthday the same as Amy's?
不过我们没有要盛大庆祝  她才一岁
Yeah, but we're not doing anything big 'cause she's one,
伯纳黛特在卧床养胎
Bernadette's on bed rest, and
而我是懒蛋
I'm lazy.
你们好啊
Hey, guys.
-你好啊  -你来啦
- Hello.  - Hey.
霍华德兄
Howard.
拉杰同志
Raj.
失陪了
Excuse me.
不是吧  你们还在闹别扭啊
Really? Is this still happening?
我很乐意重修旧好  但某人像个婴儿似的
I'm willing to make up, but someone's being a baby.
我最爱谜语了  我来猜猜
Ooh! I do love a riddle. Oh, let me see.
我第一个会猜哈雷
See, my first guess would be Halley,
不过骂她像个婴儿有点不合理
but that'd be strange to accuse her of being a baby
因为她本来就是婴儿
'cause she is a baby. Um...
我想或许是斯图尔特
I suppose it could be Stuart;
他的小脑袋有某种婴儿奶香
his head does have a certain milky scent.
不过嘛...
Although...
是我  谢尔顿  他是在骂我闹婴儿脾气
I-It's me, Sheldon. He-He's calling me a baby.
不好说  我今天还看到莱纳德把钥匙放嘴里
No, I don't know. I saw Leonard put his keys in his mouth today.
你都是个成年人了  别那么幼稚
You're a grown man; act like it.
内容是一个高中生的冒险故事
一个读《阿奇漫画》的人  真好意思说这种大话
Big talk coming from a guy holding an Archie comic book.
这是阿奇的挚友加戈.佐纳斯的个人番外篇
《狼人加戈》比你老爸生的傻子[加戈]强多了
Hey, werewolf Jughead is not your dad's Jughead.
别这样  你们都当朋友那么多年了  别吵了
Come on, you guys have been friends forever. Quit fighting.
我有两张去
I have an extra ticket
今晚《星球大战》新电影首映的票
to the opening of The Last Jedi tonight.
本来一张要给霍华德  现在给你吧
It was gonna be Howard's, but you can have it.
过去虽美  缘分已尽
You two had a good run.
第十一季  第十一集
今晚谁想再去看一次《星战8》
Uh, who wants to go see Last Jedi again tonight?
-我要去  -我也要
- Mm, I'm in. - Me, too.
这样能补上我眨眼时错过的部分
It'll be nice to see the parts I missed while I was blinking.
各位  计划有变
Hey, guys, there's a change of plans.
我们最终还是决定为哈雷办生日派对
We are having a party for Halley's birthday after all.
原来伯纳黛特与"任何不是没心没肺恶魔"的人
Turns out Bernadette and "Anyone who's not a heartless monster"
都会觉得应该举办
thinks that's the right thing to do.
我不喜欢小孩  不过我喜欢生日蛋糕
I don't like kids, but I do like birthday cake.
等等  蛋糕上会有糖霜裱花吗
Oh, wait, will there be sugary icing flowers on it?
我不知道
I don't know.
我愿意以身犯险
I'll risk it.
如果我闹脾气又提早走  原因不言而喻
But if I have a tantrum and have to leave early, you'll know why.
-给你  -给你
- Here you go. - Here you go.
两位到时候见
See you two there.
你不是吧
Are you kidding me?
你不邀请我去哈雷的生日派对吗
You're not gonna invite me to Halley's birthday?
我是她的干爸  这可不是白叫
I'm her godfather; that means something.
或者...  听我说...  就是白叫
Or-- hear me out on this-- it doesn't.
好了  够了
Okay, that's enough.
你们俩要么别吵了  要么吵点新花样出来
This fight either has to end or get way more entertaining.
没事  我受够他了
Don't worry about it 'cause I'm done putting up with him!
我知道你有很多事要烦
I know you have a lot on your mind,
但你觉得什么时候能知道蛋糕裱花的事
but when do you think we'll have an answer on those cake flowers?
你在看什么
What you reading?
是你哥哥的圣诞卡片
Oh, it's your brother's Christmas letter.
如果里面有他跟他老婆孩子
If there's a picture of his wife and his kids
还有他家的狗与马  全部穿成套睡衣的照片
and his dogs and his horses all in matching pajamas,
我求你烧了它
I beg you to burn it.
他们穿的睡衣上有小马
Aw, the people's pajamas have little horses on them,
而他家的马穿的衣服上有小人
and the horses' have little people.
他就是趁机炫耀他生活多完美
It's just his chance to brag about how great his life is.
别这样  挺好的啊
Oh, come on, it's nice.
你知道他合作的公益机构吗
You know that nonprofit he works with?
他们在非洲卢旺达盖了医院呢
They built a hospital in Rwanda.
快来看我  我在卢旺达盖了医院呢
Look at me. I built a hospital in Rwanda.
好有道理啊  我都没这么想过呢
That is a good point. I hadn't thought of it that way.
-两位好  -好
- Hello. - Hey.
这是艾米生日要用的  我能先放这里吗
So this is for Amy's birthday. Can I leave it here?
行啊  那是什么
Sure. What is it?
黄油搅拌筒
A butter churn.
我也要送她那个呢
Aw, that's what I got her.
这是我给她的拓荒者惊喜生日晚餐上要用的
It's for her surprise frontier birthday dinner.
我要做压缩饼干  盐煮猪肉
I am making hardtack, boiled salt pork,
因为是特殊的日子  还要做可嚼式树汁块
and because it's a special day, a chewable gob of tree sap.
那个味道好吗
Is that good?
跟其他食物相比  不好
Uh, compared to other foods, no.
跟树的其他部位相比嘛...
Compared to other parts of a tree?
在晚餐过后  我们会进行生日交媾
And then after dinner, we will have birthday coitus.
你觉得这部分符合历史吗
Do you think that will also be historically accurate?
我猜会像其他开拓者的生活一样
I assume like the rest of frontier life,
既累人又简短
it'll be exhausting and short.
你才又累人又短小呢
You're exhausting and short.
斯图尔特  你会来哈雷的生日派对吧
Hey, Stuart, you're coming to Halley's party, right?
那当然
You bet.
而且  我住在那里又收到邀请
Plus, I live there and I was invited,
这已经比我十岁生日派对还赞了
so it's already better than my tenth birthday party.
太好了  你能带几样东西来吗
Great. Can you bring a few things?
行啊  你要什么
Sure. What do you need?
气球  彩带
Balloons, streamers,
冰块  零食  蹦跳城堡  脸部彩绘颜料
ice, snacks, a bounce house, face painter,
还有几个小孩  他们家长会愿意替我说谎
and a couple kids whose parents are willing to lie and say
说他们是在我从未去过的"亲子班"认识我的
they know me from the Daddy and Me class I've never been to.
那你每周都跟哈雷去哪里了啊
Where do you and Halley go every week?
反正重要的是我一直陪在她身边
The important thing is we're together,
电影太暴力时  我都会捂上她眼睛
and if the movie gets too violent, I cover her eyes.
别太紧张这个派对
Don't stress about this party.
她才一岁  她什么都不会记得
She's one; she's not gonna remember.
之前我让她看自己的脚趾  她吓坏了
The other day I showed her her toe, and she was shocked.
派对不是为了孩子  是为了孩子她妈
It's not for the baby; it's for Bernadette.
她对错过
She's feeling guilty
哈雷的成长点滴感到愧疚
about all the stuff she's missing with Halley.
好吧
All right.
斯图尔特叔叔帮你忙
Uncle Stuart's got your back.
斯图尔特式派对绝对与众不同
Ain't no party like a Stuart party
因为斯图尔特从没被邀请去过派对
because Stuart's never invited to parties.
停电了吗
Did the electricity go out?
女士  我不知道你说的"电"是什么
I don't know what you mean by "electricity," Ma'am.
我只是一个住在草原小屋里的务农男孩
I am just a farmer boy living in a little house on the prairie.
你开心就好
I'm glad you're happy.
我想在你生日的时候做点特别的
I wanted to do something special for your birthday.
有  很特别  太完美了
Oh, you did, you did! It's perfect!
但你知道我生日是明天的吧
You do know that my birthday's tomorrow, right?
这只是你的生日周末第一阶段
This is just step one of your birthday weekend.
你愿意坐下与我一同享用
Now, would you care to join me
正宗拓荒者晚餐吗
for an authentic frontier dinner
全部手工做的呢
made entirely from scratch?
真不敢相信你做了这些  太棒了
I can't believe you did this. It's amazing!
没什么大不了的啦
Oh, it's not a big deal.
怕你误会  这的确是有大不了
Just to be clear, it was a big deal.
我刚才只是谦虚  你有听懂的吧
I was being modest. You got that, right?
如雷贯耳
Loud and clear.
希望你已经饿了
Well, I hope you're hungry.
我饿死了
Oh, I'm starving.
太好了  饥饿的确也符合那个年代背景
Oh, good. Starvation is authentic to the time period.
如果你还得了疟疾
If you also have malaria
与十分不信任美洲原住民
and a deep distrust of Native Americans,
我们就真是有地道的拓荒者风了
we're really cooking with a woodstove.
那是黄油吗
Is that butter?
是啊  但配饼干省着点抹啊
Yes. But don't blow it all on one biscuit.
我花了9小时才搅出那么多
Took me nine hours to make that.
可能都得了搅拌者肘
I think I got churner's elbow.
我知道我们只在生日那天交媾
I know we only have coitus on my birthday,
但我都不知道我能不能忍到午夜过后了
but I don't know if I can wait until midnight.
你到时候会庆幸你忍住了的
Oh, well, you'll be glad you did.
全天下谁不知道最棒的前戏
Everyone knows the best foreplay
就是严格遵守时间表
is rigid adherence to a strict schedule.
你在干嘛
Hey. What are you doing?
我决定也设计一封我的圣诞贺卡
Oh, I've decided to write my own Christmas letter.
我正在列下我们今年做过的牛逼事
So I'm gonna make a list of all the cool things we did this year.
有意思  能帮忙吗
Oh, fun. Can I help?
可以啊  你想到今年做的任何牛逼事了吗
Yes. Can you think of a single cool thing we did this year?
我们的工作都进展不错啊
Uh, well, both of our jobs are going great.
大概吧  我的空军项目被拿回了
Sure. I mean, my Air Force project got taken away,
你也不是真的很爱当药代
and you're not crazy about selling pharmaceuticals.
我就写"工作还在"
I'll just write down "Still employed."
我们结婚两周年了
Oh, we had our second anniversary.
不过我们也没怎么记得它
Uh, yeah, but we did kind of forget about it,
就写"婚姻还在"
so maybe just write "Still married."
很好  行
Great. Okay.
这是个好开头
Okay, that's a start.
还有什么
What else?
其实或许这样就够了
You know, maybe this is enough.
来看看我们今年的照片吧  有助于回忆
Let's look at our pictures; that-that'll jog our memories.
那照片是干嘛的
What is that a picture of?
那是我背上的一个痣
Oh, uh, that's a mole on my back.
我想确定它不是黑色素瘤
I wanted to make sure it wasn't growing.
你是怎么能拍到自己的背啊
How'd you get a picture of your own back?
谢尔顿拍的  我们是检查痣小伙伴
Sheldon took it. We're kind of mole buddies.
这照片挺有爱啊
Hey, that's a cute picture.
这不是我们差点要去海边那次拍的吗
Isn't that the day we almost went to the beach?
阵亡将士纪念日吗
Memorial Day?
不是  那天是我们差点就去爬山那次
No, that was the day we almost went to the mountains.
这就是加州的一个优点
That's the great thing about California;
你能在同一天同时
you can almost go to the mountains
差点去海边又差点去爬山
and almost go to the beach in the same day.
是啊
Yeah.
对不起  我故意不邀请你
Look, I'm sorry about not inviting you
来参加哈雷的生日派对  这太恶劣了
to Halley's birthday. That wasn't cool.
我们很希望你能来  给
And of course we would love to have you. Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
我也很乐意来参加
I'd really like to be there.
太好了  因为派对是明天  我需要你来筹办
Great, 'cause it's tomorrow, and I need you to plan it.
什么
What?
斯图尔特本来说好了帮忙
Stuart was gonna help,
但免费诊所有个免费结肠镜检查机会
but the free clinic had an open spot for a colonoscopy,
他毫不犹豫弃我而去
and he jumped on it.
所以你来道歉
So-so-so you're just apologizing
是因为你需要帮忙吗
because you need something?
对啊  我觉得我敢承认是很成熟的一件事呢
Yes, and I think it's pretty mature of me to admit it.
这也太羞辱人了吧
Well, that's very insulting.
是啊  你到底帮不帮忙
Right again. Are you gonna help me or not?
不  我才不要帮你
No, I will not help you.
但我愿意帮哈雷
But I will help Halley.
她是我干女儿  我爱她
She's my goddaughter, and I love her.
而且我还有很多
And I have a lot of party favors
小桂子生日派对多余的派对道具...
left over from Cinnamon's birthday, so...
希望她会喜欢咬了会发声的东西
I hope she likes things that squeak when you chew on them.
她是人类  不是动物
Sh-She's a human being, not an animal.
但感觉会很受欢迎呢
But that actually would be a hit.
你还想要什么吗
Can I get you anything else?
不用了  谢谢  我吃饱了
No, thanks. I think I'm good.
你确定吗  还剩很多猪油呢
You sure? There's still plenty of pork fat.
不过如果我们不吃
Although, if we don't eat it,
我们是也可以把它做成肥皂啦
I suppose we could turn it into soap.
那样说不定还会好吃点
That might taste better.
我想过去做在沙发上歇会儿
I think I'm just gonna go over here and sit on the couch.
好啊
Oh, great.
那我们进行第二阶段吧
Then we will move on to stage two:
拨雨撩云
the pitching of woo.
撩吧
Ooh.
要我给你念念淫秽的19世纪打油诗吗
Should I read you some bawdy 19th century limericks?
好吧
Okay.
来
Oh, here.
"泰瑞豪特来了一牧师
"There once was a priest from Terre Haute
他买了一绵羊一山羊..."
who purchased a sheep and a goat..."
等等
Hold on a second.
是不是有点越来越热啊
Is it getting hot in here?
我都还没读到淫秽的部分呢
Well, I didn't even get to the dirty part yet.
不是  我是说认真的
No, I-I'm serious.
你觉得会是食物有问题吗
Do you think there was something wrong with that food?
拓荒者扇贝吗  应该不会吧
Frontier scallops? I shouldn't think so.
我的肚子有点难受
My stomach's feeling a little weird.
我的也有一点
Yeah. Uh, mine, too.
我确定这只是情欲高涨前的剧烈疼痛
I'm sure it's just the first sharp cramps of arousal.
不  这感觉不太对
No. Th-This doesn't feel right.
别急  色色的话留到卧室里说
Hey, hey, save that sexy talk for the bedroom.
不好意思  失陪一下
You know, if you'll excuse me,
我去洗把脸
I am just going to go freshen up.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
给我一分钟
I'll be out in a minute.
我等不了一分钟
I don't have a minute!
真不敢相信你一个晚上就弄到这样
I can't believe you pulled this all together overnight.
国际知名的三人打击乐团  表演时会浑身涂成蓝色
如果有更多时间  我能请来蓝人乐团呢
Uh, if I had more time, I could have gotten the Blue Man Group.
其中一个跟我去同一个干洗店
One of them goes to my dry cleaner.
顺带一说  超讨厌他
Who, by the way, hates him.
你真是帮了大忙了
You really saved the day.
不是为了帮你  是为了哈雷
Well, it's not for you. It's for Halley.
我也相信她一定会很感谢你
And I'm sure she'd appreciate it,
如果她能懂这是在干嘛与你是谁
if she knew what's going on or who you are.
早安
Morning.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
真够"快乐"的
Yeah, sure.
你有睡觉吗
Did you sleep at all?
没有  你呢
No. You?
我在马桶上晕过去了一会
I passed out on the toilet once.
不知道这算不算
I don't know if that counts.
你好点了吗
Feel any better?
糟透了
I feel terrible.
那么
Well...
现在该做爱了吗
should we make love now?
你怎么还有心思做爱呢
How can you even think about sex?
我可是大老爷们  跟大家一样一年有一次性需求
Hey, I'm a man; I have annual needs just like anyone.
再说  这是我们的生日传统
And besides, it's our birthday tradition.
你觉得你能不能
You think you can do it
在我躺尸不动  你也不碰我的情况下做完
while I lie perfectly still and you don't touch me?
我可以尽力一试
I can try.
想再来一次吗
Want to do it again?
早上好
Morning.
"养活了'杨弛'"  杨弛是谁啊
"Kept Fern alive"? Who's Fern?
不  是羊齿  浴室里那盆羊齿蕨
No, the fern. The one in the bathroom.
我们真要硬说那盆褐色植物是活的吗  好吧
We're really calling that brown thing alive? Okay.
你想这个想多久了
So, how long have you been working on this?
几个小时吧
Oh, couple hours.
我中途休息了一会  试着打破我马里奥赛车的记录
I took a break to try to beat my high score on Mario Kart.
你打破了吗
Well, did you do it?
你在板子上看到这一条了吗
Do you see it on the board?
这太蠢了  我们的生活很美满啊
Okay, this is silly. Our lives are great.
我也这么觉得
I think so, too.
那你为什么如此烦恼
So then why is this bugging you so much?
我想是因为  感觉大家都在前进
I guess it feels like everyone's moving forward
而我们却原地踏步
and we're stuck.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我们已经结婚两年了
Well, we've been married two years.
是否该考虑接下来的事了
Should we think about what's next?
比如买栋房子  或是生个娃
Like buying a house or having a baby?
有一天我想完成这些步骤
Look, I want to do all those things someday,
但在那之前我还有很多想做的事
but there's a bunch of stuff I want to do first.
好吧  比如什么事
Okay, like what?
我也不知道  保持苗条和有钱
I don't know, stay thin and have money.
不  我是认真的
No, no, I-I'm serious.
如果有想做的事  我们就开始去做吧
If there's things we want to do, let's start doing them.
好吧  我们从来没有一起正式旅行过
Okay. Well, we've never been on a big trip together.
我很愿意去
I would love that.
那你的信里可以写这个啦
Okay, there's something for your letter:
"有考虑过去旅行"
"Considered going on a trip."
虽然只是一天游
It's just a day trip,
但我们可以坐船到卡特琳娜岛
but we could take the ferry out to Catalina.
很好啊  我们就去吧
Great, let's do it.
艾米占用了洗手间  我需要...
Amy's in the bathroom and I need to...!
我仿佛已经听见了海的声音
It's like I can hear the ocean already.
好的  谢谢告知
Okay. Thanks for letting me know.
怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
伯纳黛特家人的孩子们病了  他们不来了
Bernadette's sister's kids are sick and they're not coming.
但就是为了他们  杯子蛋糕才做成素食啊
But they're the whole reason the cupcakes are vegan!
-派对布置得怎么样啦  -很好
- How's the party coming? - Good!
超棒  亲友们马上就要到啦
Great! Our friends should be here any second!
除了我们  你只邀请了他们吗
Those are the only other people you invited?
"爸比与我"班上的那些孩子呢
What about the kids from the Daddy and Me class?
成熟点吧
Oh, grow up.
-糟了  -怎么了
- Uh-oh. - What?
我没把食物放进冰箱
I left the food out.
你担心会变质成安全食品吗
You afraid it's gonna go good?
你感觉怎么样了
How are you feeling?
我胃疼  恶寒
Ugh. My stomach aches, I got the chills,
嘴巴里的味道怪怪的
my mouth tastes weird,
吞口水都疼
it hurts to swallow,
我看东西还有点重影
and I've got a little double vision.
是的
Yeah.
我也好多了
I'm feeling better, too.
这派对简直是灾难
Well, this party's a disaster.
不是派对的错啊
Don't blame the party!
你知道我托了多少关系
You know how many favors I had to call in
才租到神奇女侠的蹦跳城堡吗
with my bounce house guy to get Wonder Woman?
那是神奇女侠吗
Is that Wonder Woman?
严格来说  那是个中国山寨版
Technically, it's a Chinese knockoff called
叫快乐强壮的泳衣女士
Happy Strong Swimsuit Lady.
那我把话收回  这派对棒极了
Then I take it back; it's a great party.
你自己坐在这儿生闷气吧
Well, you can sit here and sulk if you want.
我要去庆祝哈雷的第一个生日
I'm gonna go celebrate Halley's first birthday.
这个派对是我计划的  你屁忙都没帮
Which I planned with no help from you.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
这是蹦跳城堡  我要进去蹦
It's a bounce house! I'm gonna go bounce in it!
进去前  应该要先脱鞋啊
You're supposed to take your shoes off before you go in there!
你知道吗
You know what?
我女儿的生日派对已经让我压力很大了
I'm stressed about my daughter's birthday party.
我不要再看你脸色
I don't need your attitude.
我很努力把派对办起来
Well, I worked really hard on this,
你连句谢谢都没说
and you haven't even said thank you.
真抱歉  谢谢啊
Oh, I'm sorry. Thank you.
谢谢你把你生活里
Thank you for blaming me
一切不顺都怪到我头上
for everything that's wrong in your life!
谢谢你抛弃了我们的友谊
Thank you for walking out on our friendship!
不客气
You are welcome!
我也谢谢你这些年来不断吐槽我
And thank you for mocking me for all of these years!
谢谢你这么多槽点
Thank you for making it so easy!
你为什么这么混蛋
Why are you being such a jerk?
因为你是我最好的朋友  而你伤了我的心
Because you're my best friend and you hurt my feelings!
你也是我最好的朋友  你也伤了我的心
Well, you're my best friend and you hurt my feelings!
真不敢相信你居然推我
I can't believe you shoved me!
我也不敢相信你居然推我
Well, I can't believe you shoved me!
但还挺好玩的  不是吗
But it was kind of fun, wasn't it?!
-是的  再推一次  -乐意至极
- It was! Do it again! - Gladly!
好  现在同时互推
Okay, now at the same time!
真是太赞了
Oh, oh, that was awesome!
好  这次先膝盖着地  然后站起来
Yeah, okay, this time, knees, then feet.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
再来  再来
Again! Again!
大家好呀
Hello.
你们来了
You made it.
你们俩感觉怎么样
How you two feeling?
好点了
Oh, a little better.
那些书应该叫
Those books should have been called
《草原茅厕》才对
Little Outhouse on the Prairie.
哈雷醒了  准备好参加派对啦
Halley's awake and ready for her party!
我这就上来
Be right up!
我想看小寿星女
Ooh, I want to see the birthday girl.
我很想见她
I'd love to see her.
别那么快  重新穿上这胸罩需要点时间
Walk slow, it takes a while to get this bra back on.
其实...
You know...
你的生日还没过
it's still your birthday.
确实
It is.
我们两个  都感觉好多了
And... we are both... feeling better.
确实
We are.
那间弹跳屋里没人
And there's no one in that bounce house.
哎
No.
太棒了
Great.
我们去里面跳一会
Let's go jump for a bit,
再找个房间交媾吧
and then find a bedroom to have coitus in.